Guide to the John L. Hennessy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0700
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 2004-2005; Accession ARCH-2007-164
  - Education, School of, 05/15/2002-07/28/2005; AA 4.5 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Hoover Institute, 08/27/2004-08/29/2005; AA 4.9 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Learning Lab, Larry/Sweden/Global Learning Institute Wallenburg, 09/27/2004; AA 4.10.4 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - CISAC, 10/14/2004-05/23/2005; AA 4.10.6 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Latin American Studies, Center for, 9/20/2004-01/30/2005; AA 4.11 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Libraries, Stanford, 05/08/2002-08/29/2005; AA 4.12 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - School of Law, 04/29/2004-07/15/2005; AA 4.15 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - ITSS, 09/27/2004-03/17/2005; AA 4.22 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Awards/Prizes, Misc., 09/30/2002-08/24/2005; AA 5 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Nobel Prizes, 02/01/2005; AA 5.1 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 03/30/2004; AA 5.2 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Presidential Scholars, 06/03/2002; AA 5.3 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Grants, Scholarships, Misc., 10/15/2003-08/22/2005; AA 6 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Fellowships, Misc/General Information, 10/29/2002-08/04/2005; AA 8 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Fulbright Fellowship/Scholarship, 09/07/2004-03/14/2005; AA 8.16 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 09/09/2004-06/22/2005; AA 8.25 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Terman Fellowship, 04/08/2005; AA 8.30 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Tanner Lectures, 10/20/2004-06/29/2005; AA 9.19 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Miscellaneous, 11/10/2003-05/18/2005; AA 10 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Stanford Mansion/Stanford Misc, 09/07/2004-08/31/2005; AD 1 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Founders Day and Historical Society, 01/19/2005; AD 1.2 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - ROTC, 05/24/2005; AD 2.26 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - President's Office/ John Hennessy, 11/19/2004-08/16/2005; AD 4 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Presidential Lecture Symposium Human & Arts (PLSHA), 11/01/2004-05/12/2005; AD 4.2 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Workshop on Gender Equity, 04/01/2002; AD 4.3 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - General Correspondence (1 of 2), 09/01/2004-01/21/2005; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - General Correspondence (2 of 2), 01/21/2005-08/30/2005; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Clippings/Editorials, 10/14/2004-02/23/2005; AD 4.20.1 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Condolence Letters, 09/21/2004-08/29/2005; AD 4.20.2 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 11/19/2004-08/30/2005; AD 4.20.3 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Letters of Appreciation, 09/01/2004-08/30/2005; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Invitations (1 of 4), 10/27/2003-11/23/2004; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Invitations ( 2 of 4), 11/24/2004-02/15/2005; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Invitations (3 of 4), 02/17/2005-05/09/2005; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Invitations (4 of 4), 05/10/2005-08/30/2005; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Nonsense, 09/05/2004-08/31/2005; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Search/Recommendation, 12/07/2004; AD 4.20.6 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Recommendation Letters, Students, 09/29/2004-01/15/2005; AD 4.20.6/1 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Complaint Letters, 09/20/2004-08/22/2005; AD 4.20.7 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Solicitation Letters (1 of 3), 10/14/2003-01/13/2005; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Solicitation Letters (2 of 3), 01/18/2005-04/19/2005; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Solicitation Letters (3 of 3), 04/19/2005-08/31/2005; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - University Communications, 10/12/2004-08/31/2005; AD 4.22 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Campus Relations, 05/13/2002-01/31/2005; AD 6 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Admissions (1 of 2), 09/09/2004-01/05/2005; AD 8.1 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Admissions (2 of 2), 01/07/2005-08/30/2005; AD 8.1 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Student Affairs, 09/22/2004-07/18/2005; AD 8.8 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Vaden Student Health Center, 01/19/2005; AD 8.9 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Overseas Studies, 10/14/2004-08/01/2005; AD 8.11 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Financial Aid, 02/15/2005; AD 8.12 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 03/03/2004-09/22/2005; AD 8.18 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Housing/Dining Services-Students, 02/21/2005-05/23/2005; AD 8.18.11 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Registrar - Bursar, 12/10/2004-08/01/2005; AD 8.21 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations (Human Resources), 04/21/2003-08/04/2005; AD 10 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Stanford Labor Action Coalition, 03/19/2002-05/20/2005; AD 10SLAC (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Employment Inquiries, 09/02/2004-08/30/2005; AD 10.1 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Outdoor Art, Committee, 05/06/2005-05/14/2005; AD 10.7.4 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Events, Stanford and the Public, 11/17/2004-08/19/2005; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Lively Arts at Stanford, 09/10/2004-06/23/2005; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Freshman Orientation, 09/13/2004-08/23/2005; AD 11.7.7 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - External Media & Publications, 11/01/2004-04/14/2005; AD 11.8 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Stanford University Press, 02/07/2005-05/29/2005; AD 11.8.9 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Surveys, Questionnaires, 08/10/2001-08/30/2005; AD 11.8.10 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Stanford Media & Publications, 02/25/2005-07/11/2005; AD 11.8.11 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Controller's Office, 09/30/2004-08/08/2005; AD 12.2 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Stanford Management Company, 08/26/2003-07/01/2005; AD 12.3 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Budget, Tim Warner, 06/28/2005; AD 12.5 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Development - John Ford Stuff, 09/02/2003-07/19/2005; AD 12.10 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Development Office, Misc., 12/02/2004; AD 12.10.1 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - President's Discretionary, 11/12/2004; AD 12.10.2 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Stanford Fund, 11/18/2004-08/01/2005; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Asian Relations, General (1 of 2), 09/09/2004-01/13/2005; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Asian Relations, General (2 of 2), 1/13/2005-08/20/2005; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - University Seminars (Development), 05/18/2005; AD 12.10.3/13 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Land Use and Buildings General, 06/05/2002-08/30/2005; AD 12.14 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Art Gallery & Museums (Not Cantor), 01/12/2005; AD 12.14.7/1 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 10/14/2004-08/31/2005; AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Facilities Planning/University Architect, 01/15/2002-08/09/2005; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Memorial Church, 09/24/2003-01/31/2005; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Parking & Transportation, 01/10/2005-07/20/2005; AD 12.14.7/53 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Conferences, Misc., 09/02/2004-08/24/2005; AD 13.10.1 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Alumni Relations, 09/14/2004-08/24/2005; AL 1 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Stanford Parents, 09/08/2004-03/15/2005; AL 1.1/1 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 10/30/2003-08/26/2005; AL 1.3 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Alumni Events, 09/01/2004-08/11/2005; AL 1.7 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Stanford Alumni Association, 09/08/2004-12/10/2004; AL 3 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Government Relations, 03/16/2001-07/20/2005; G 1 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - California State Government, 09/13/2004-08/17/2005; G 1.2 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - U.S. Governmental Relations, 09/02/2004-08/10/2005; G 3 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Department of Defense (DoD), 05/26/2004-04/26/2005; G 3.7 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Department of Energy (DoE), 04/07/2003-08/29/2005; G 3.7.2 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - National Aeronautics & Space Administration (NASA), 03/01/2005-05/12/2005; G 3.7.4 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Health & Human Services, Office of Civil Rights, 09/27/2004; G 3.8.1 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH), 09/14/2004; G 3.8.2 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Department of Education, U.S. (USDE), 09/17/2004-07/25/2005; G 3.8.3 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - NSF - National Science Foundation, 11/15/2004-03/15/2005; G 3.19 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Local Government / Local Business, 02/08/2005-08/03/2005; G 4 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Foreign Government Relations, misc., 06/01/2004-08/01/2005; G 5 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - CA Institute for Federal Policy Research, 04/07/2005-07/13/2005; G 7 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Stanford Health Services/Kaiser, 09/24/2001-12/06/2004; SHS 3 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Packard Children's Hospital, 1/10/2005-08/30/2005; SHS 7 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 05/10/2004-08/22/2005; SHS 9 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Hospitals, Centers & Clinics, 11/26/2003-12/08/2003; SHS 13 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 09/30/2003-08/15/2005; M 1 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Medical School, Misc., 08/08/2002-06/17/2005; M 5 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Institute for Cancer/Stem Cell Biology & Med., 09/03/2004-03/02/2005; M 5.1 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Organizations, Misc. (1 of 4), 03/08/2001-11/08/2004; O 1 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Organizations, Misc. (2 of 4), 11/10/2004-12/15/2004; O 1 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Organizations, Misc. (3 of 4), 12/15/2004-04/05/2005; O 1 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Organizations, Misc. (4 of 4), 04/05/2005-08/30/2005; O 1 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Council on Competitiveness, 10/7/2004-08/26/2005; O 1.2 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities (AAC&U), 08/30/2002-03/15/2005; O 3 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 10/13/2004-06/17/2005; O 3.1 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Consortium of Social Science Association, 09/21/2004-08/31/2005; O 3.3 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Association Pacific Rim University, 12/12/2002-08/30/2005; O 3.4 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 09/20/2004-07/07/2005; O 3.7 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - American Council on Education, 08/30/2004-08/22/2005; O 3.8 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 10/12/2004-03/22/2005; O 3.10 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - The College Board, 09/14/2004-05/24/2005; O 3.25 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), 06/11/2003; O 3.38 (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - National Academies, 09/30/2002-08/30/2005; O 3.43 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 09/08/2004-08/25/2005; O 3.44 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 09/30/2004-08/31/2005; O 3.47 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - CA Business of Higher Education (BHEF), 11/24/2004-08/29/2005; O 3.56 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Korn/Ferry International, 11/29/2004-08/30/2005; O 5.1 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Political Groups, Misc., 07/05/2005; O 6 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Research Organizations, 09/20/2004-06/06/2005; O 7 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Council of Presidents, University Research Associates, 10/25/2004-04/04/2005; O 7.16 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Colleges and Universities (1 of 4), 03/11/2003-12/06/2004; O 8 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Colleges and Universities (2 of 4), 12/06/2004-03/14/2005; O 8 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Colleges and Universities (3 of 4), 03/15/2005-04/29/2005; O 8 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Colleges and Universities (4 of 4), 05/02/2005-08/30/2005; O 8 (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU), 09/09/2004-08/22/2005; O 8.7 (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities, 9/24/2004-03/30/2005; O 8.9 (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - Caltech, 08/13/2003; O 8.16 (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Columbia University, 03/01/2005-04/11/2005; O 8.18 (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Cornell University, 02/15/2005-07/19/2005; O 8.19 (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - Harvard University, 09/02/2003-05/17/2005; O 8.23 (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Peking University, 11/16/2004-06/29/2005; O 8.30 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Princeton University, 12/06/2004-04/05/2005; O 8.36 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Univ. of CA (All Campuses), 10/13/2004-08/31/2005; O 8.43 (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - University of Michigan, 02/07/2005-04/22/2005; O 8.45 (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - University of Southern California, 02/01/2004-03/15/2005; O 8.49 (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Western Association of Schools and Colleges (WASC), 07/14/2000-02/24/2005; O 8.52 (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Yale University, 01/25/2005; O 8.53 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Other Inaugurations, 09/01/2004-08/15/2005; O 8.55 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 09/01/2004-07/18/2005; O 11 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - American Philosophical Society, 09/01/2004; O 15 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Research Misc., 10/06/2003-08/25/2005; R 0 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Women & Gender, 10/19/2004-07/25/2005; R 1.8 (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Institute for International Studies (IIS), 07/17/2003-08/22/2005; R 1.12 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Initiative On The Environment, 10/26/04-08/01/2005; R 4.2 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Stanford Leadership Institute, 06/30/2006; R 7 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - The Science Coalition, 12/12/2004; R 8 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Student, Misc, 02/04/2004-08/01/2005; ST 1 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Student (Groups), 09/16/2004-02/02/2005; ST 1.1 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - ASSU, 02/04/2004-06/06/2005; ST 2 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Bechtel International Center, 08/15/2005-08/22/2005; ST 3.5 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Student Radio, KZSU, 02/12/2005-07/18/2005; ST 3.18 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Haas Center, 08/02/2004-08/31/2005; ST 3.29 (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - Gardner, John - Fellowship, 04/28/2000-06/06/2003; ST 3.29/1 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Campus Compact, 11/25/2003-04/19/2005; ST 3.35 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Asian Pacific Scholarship Program, 05/09/2005; ST 7.1 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 10/11/2004-08/22/2005; ST 8 (Box 8, Folder 198)
- President's records concerning WASC, 1991-2000; Accession ARCH-2007-326
  - WASC Accreditation Self-Study report (printout), 2000 Jan (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - WASC report, 1991; 1 optical disc (CD-ROM) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - WASC report (binder containing printout), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - WASC report, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - WASC report document abstracts, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- President's records, 2005-2006; Accession ARCH-2008-057
  - Provost's Office, 09/28/2005-11/04/2005; AA 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, 04/20/2006; AA 1.12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Education, 10/07/2003-09/26/2005; AA 1.13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Emeriti, 06/24/2005-04/24/2006; AA 2.2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty/Staff Affirmative Action, 02/01/2006; AA 2.3.3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Development/Affairs, 10/04/2004-06/01/2006; AA 2.7 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Fellows, 10/25/2005-04/27/2006; AA 2.9 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Education, 09/15/2005-08/11/2006; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Accreditation Issues, 09/27/2005-08/25/2006; AA 3.4 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ratings/Rankings, 01/10/2006-06/06/2006; AA 3.5 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cultures, Ideas & Values, 08/27/2006; AA 3.5.1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Humanities & Sciences, School of, 09/12/2005-08/25/2006; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Humanities Center, 05/01/2006-08/21/2006; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - MLK, Jr. Research & Education, 10/26/2005-02/09/2006; AA 4.1.1/3 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - SICA, 03/26/2006; AA 4.1.1/4 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Applied Physics, Dept. of, 10/09/2005; AA 4.1.8 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Art, Dept. of, 09/09/2003-06/06/2006; AA 4.1.9 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chemistry, Dept. of, 10/4/2005-08/25/2006; AA 4.1.13 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dance, Dept. of, 37384; AA 4.1.16 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Computer Science, Dept. of, 12/20/2005-06/17/2006; AA 4.1.17 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Drama, Dept. of, 10/26/2005-07/12/2006; AA 4.1.18 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - SIEPR, 09/01/2005-06/09/2006; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - French & Italian, Dept. of, 11/14/2005-05/16/2006; AA 4.1.22 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - History, Dept. of, 11/03/2005; AA 4.1.25 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 12/19/2005-04/19/2006; AA 4.1.28 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Music, Dept. of, 10/11/2005-06/18/2006; AA 4.1.29 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Athletics, Dept. of, 09/01/2005-08/21/2006; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Football Games, 09/12/2005-08/23/2006; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 10/06/2005-08/24/2006; AA 4.1.32 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Physics, Dept. of, 10/05/2005; AA 4.1.33 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Political Science, Dept. of, 11/01/2005-11/02/2005; AA 4.1.34 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 01/24/2006-02/23/2006; AA 4.1.35 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - GSB, 09/20/2005-07/24/2006; AA 4.2 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Earth Sciences, School of, 04/06/2006-04/27/2006; AA 4.3 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - GCEP, 08/03/2006-08/14/2006; AA 4.3.1 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Engineering, School of, 09/27/2005-08/15/2006; AA 4.4 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Education, School of, 09/30/2005-05/18/2006; AA 4.5 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Hoover Institution, 09/06/2005-07/27/2006; AA 4.9 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - SCIL, 09/30/2005-11/29/2005; AA 4.10.4 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - CISAC, 09/13/2005-06/08/2006; AA 4.10.6 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - CREEES, 10/04/2005-10/13/2005; AA 4.11.1 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - SULAIR, 03/18/2005-08/18/2006; AA 4.12 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Law, School of, 11/04/2005-08/15/2006; AA 4.15 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - IT Services & Admin. Systems, 09/10/2005-07/24/2006; AA 4.22 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Awards & Prizes, Misc., 05/23/2003-08/26/2006; AA 5 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 02/28/2006-05/09/2006; AA 5.2 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - President's Scholars, 11/23/2005-12/02/2005; AA 5.3 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Grants & Scholarships, Miscellaneous, 09/02/2005-08/01/2006; AA 6 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Fellowships, Miscellaneous, 9/27/2005-08/26/2006; AA 8 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Fulbright Fellowship/Scholarships, 11/10/2005-07/05/2006; AA 8.16 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, 04/11/2006; AA 8.17 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 06/16/2006; AA 8.25 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Terman Fellows, 04/13/2006; AA 8.30 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Tanner Lectures, 02/22/2006; AA 9.19 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Faculty/Prof. Chairs, 10/17/2005-04/19/2006; AA 10 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Stanford Miscellaneous, 07/07/2005-08/23/2006; AD 1 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Stanford Historical Society, 11/08/2005; AD 1.2 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - ROTC, 10/24/2005; AD 2.26 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Judicial Affairs, 12/02/2005-08/18/2006; AD 3.10 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - President's Office, 10/24/2005-07/19/2006; AD 4 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, General (1 of 3), 07/05/2005-11/28/2005; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, General (2 of 3), 11/29/2005-01/17/2006; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence, General (3 of 3), 01/17/2006-08/22/2006; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - News articles, 09/22/2005-05/31/2006; AD 4.20.1 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Condolence Letters, 04/04/2005-08/21/2006; AD 4.20.2 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 10/07/2004-08/29/2008; AD 4.20.3 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Appreciation Letters, 01/31/2005-08/28/2006; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Invitations (1 of 4), 09/02/2005-12/12/2005; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Invitations (2 of 4), 12/15/2005-03/31/2006; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Invitations (3 of 4), 04/03/2006-06/05/2006; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Invitations (4 of 4), 06/05/2006-08/28/2006; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Nonsense (1 of 2), 09/01/2005-04/05/2006; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Nonsense (2 of 2), 04/07/2006-08/22/2006; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Recommendation Letters, 10/31/2005-04/25/2006; AD 4.20.6 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Recommendation, Students, 03/17/2005-08/25/2006; AD 4.20.6/1 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Complaint Letters, 01/28/2006-08/17/2006; AD 4.20.7 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Solicitations (1 of 4), 01/04/2005-11/17/2005; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Solicitations (2 of 4), 11/17/2005-01/30/2006; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Solicitations (3 of 4), 02/02/2006-05/31/2006; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Solicitations (4 of 4), 06/02/2006-08/29/2006; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - University Communications, 09/01/2005-04/13/2006; AD 4.22 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Admissions (1 of 2), 09/01/2005-04/17/2006; AD 8.1 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Admissions (2 of 2), 04/17/2006-08/30/2006; AD 8.1 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Student Affairs, 09/02/2005-05/31/2006; AD 8.8 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Bing Overseas Studies, 09/13/2005-06/16/2006; AD 8.11 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Financial Aid, 01/27/2006-07/17/2006; AD 8.12 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 04/08/2003; AD 8.18.2 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Residential & Dining Enterprises, 09/26/2005-08/18/2006; AD 8.18.11 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Registrar, 01/26/2006-08/15/2006; AD 8.21 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Human Resources, 09/08/2005-08/15/2006; AD 10 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - SLAC/CLJ, 10/12/2004-06/21/2006; AD 10-SLAC/CLJ (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Employment Inquiries, 05/01/2006-08/28/2006; AD 10.1 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - United Stanford Employees, 09/27/2005-01/12/2006; AD 10.7.8 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Events, Stanford and Public, 09/19/2005-08/25/2006; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Lively Arts, 11/14/2005-07/12/2006; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Freshman Issues, 09/30/2005-08/03/2006; AD 11.7.7 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Media & Publications Misc. (1 of 3), 11/29/2004-03/31/2006; AD 11.8 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Media & Publications Misc. (2 of 3), 04/03/2006-06/15/2006; AD 11.8 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Media & Publications Misc. (3 of 3), 06/16/2006-08/28/2006; AD 11.8 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Surveys, Questionnaires, 09/12/2005-08/18/2006; AD 11.8.10 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Media & Publications (internal), 05/17/2004-08/25/2006; AD 11.8.11 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Business Affairs, CFO, 10/17/2005-03/11/2006; AD 12.2 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Stanford Management Company, 10/26/2005-04/25/2006; AD 12.3 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Tuition, 08/01/2006-08/21/2006; AD 12.5.4 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Office of Development, 09/20/2005-07/21/2006; AD 12.10.1 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Student Fund Raising, 05/30/2006; AD 12.10.2/1 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - President's Fund, 06/08/2006; AD 12.10.2/2 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - The Stanford Fund, 12/01/2005-03/20/2006; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Hoover House Circle, Founders' Circle, 04/07/2006; AD 12.10.2/6 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - The Stanford Challenge, 04/11/2006-05/16/2006; AD 12.10.2/8 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Asian Relations, 09/30/2005-05/19/2006; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Land, BLDGS & Real Estate, 11/25/2005-08/24/2006; AD 12.14 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 09/12/2005-12/09/2005; AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Memorial Church/Religious, 10/24/2005-11/24/2005; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Parking & Transportation, 04/07/2006; AD 12.14.7/53 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Conferences, Misc. (1 of 2), 11/02/2004-01/20/2006; AD 13.10.1 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Conferences, Misc. (2 of 2), 1/23/2006-07/25/2006; AD 13.10.1 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Alumni Relations, 09/01/2005-08/18/2006; AL 1 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 05/02/2005-07/13/2006; AL 1.3 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Alumni Events, 09/22/2005-03/02/2006; AL 1.7 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Stanford Alumni Association, 02/21/2006-08/01/2006; AL 3 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - SAA 2000 (file code retired), 2005-06/05/2006; AL 3.1 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Alumni giving, general, 10/26/2006-02/23/2006; AL 5 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Government/Community Rel., 09/23/2005-07/21/2006; G 1 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - California State Government, 11/21/2005-06/12/2006; G 1.2 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - EPA, 07/21/2005-01/10/2006; G 2.3 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - U.S. Government, 09/01/2005-08/22/2006; G 3 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Defense, Dept. of, 11/08/2005-05/05/2006; G 3.7 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Energy, Dept. of, 02/08/2006-06/09/2006; G 3.7.2 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - NASA, 02/01/2006-03/22/2006; G 3.7.4 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Health & Human Services, 08/07/2006; G 3.8.1 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Education, Dept. of, 07/19/2006-08/25/2006; G 3.8.3 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 06/08/2006; G 3.18.1 (Box 5, Folder 133)